besteveralbums.com 2017-02-10

# Privacy Policy : Best Ever Albums

## Privacy Policy

**We value your privacy**  
BestEverAlbums.com knows that you care how your personal information is used and protected, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so responsibly. We take the protection of your information seriously. This policy describes our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

Please read this policy carefully because by visiting or using the BestEverAlbums.com website you give your consent that your data may be processed according to this Privacy Policy.

**What information does BestEverAlbums.com collect?**  
We collect information from you to help us personalise and improve your end-user experience and to send you communications to which you have subscribed.

The types of personal information collected during the forum registration process is kept to a minimum and is only used to provide credentials to allow you to log into the site (username, password & email address). You can choose to _voluntarily_ add additional information such as your gender, interests, occupation etc.

You can always choose not to submit the information requested, understanding that you may be unable to take advantage of some features.

On certain pages, you have the ability to participate in the forums, perform searches, create a chart, vote on polls, add favourites and interact with the data stored on this site.

We store certain types of electronic information when you interact with us on our Web site to determine popular pages, identify script errors and/or usability issues. We use "cookies" and obtain certain information from your Web browser. By transferring these alphanumeric identifiers to your computer's hard drive, we are able to recognize you during future visits to our Web site, so that you can benefit from special features, such as automatic-logon. You can disable your computer from accepting new cookies if you choose, understanding that you will then be unable to take full advantage of some of our Web site features.

We also use Web metrics tools to automatically track certain electronic information about your visits to our Web site. We use this aggregate information to do internal research on our visitors' interests and behaviour, to help us better understand and serve them. This information includes the URL that you just came from, what browser you are using, and your IP address. We use this aggregate data without connecting it with any personally identifying information.

**How secure is my personal information?**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use and transmission of your information, we have implemented the appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information that we collect from you online.

**How will BestEverAlbums.com use my information?**  
We use the information that we collect from you to enhance and personalise your user experience, and, only when you have given us permission to do so, to send you newsletters and other email communications.

We use aggregate and non-personally identifying information (such as the URL from which you arrive at our site) without using any information that would identify you. For instance, we will use this non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our Web site.

We never use or share the personally identifiable information you provide to us online in ways unrelated to the those described in this policy, nor will we share your information with third parties without your permission. Your data will only be accessible to and used by BestEverAlbums.com, and only for the purpose for which you submitted them.

Please be aware that when you click on a link on our Web site that takes you to a different Web site, you begin to interact according to the privacy policy of the other Web site. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement of any Web site you visit before providing your personal information.

**How can I access or change my personal information?**  
All Visitors: You have the right to request a copy of the personal information BestEverAlbums.com holds about you, to make any changes, and to ask that it be deleted. Please address requests to the site admin listed below.

Registered Users: If you are a BestEverAlbums.com registered user, you can access all of your personally identifying information by logging into the site and visiting your profile, My Chart and favourites pages.

You may request deletion of your BestEverAlbums.com user account by contacting a site admin. Please note that some information may possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted.

**About changes to this privacy policy**  
This privacy policy was last modified on November 10th, 2011. BestEverAlbums.com may revise this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes, we will post those amendments on our Web site so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it and how you can access or update your personal information.

**Contact details**  
Email the site administrator, webmaster at besteveralbums dot com.
